Living man online church and please go
ahead and put a one in the chat if you
are ready to get into the word of God.
Um yeah the graphics team your graphics
uh
wow I'm looking at the comments in the
chat. Put a one everyone. Put a one if
you are ready to get into the word of
God today. The message is entitled when
no man can
buy or
sell. When no man can buy or sell. Pray
with me. Heavenly
father ask Lord today that as I share
this word Lord that you would please
speak once again to your
people. Lord open our eyes. Open our
hearts.
and help us Lord to grab hold of this
message to internalize
it and that it may be lived out in our
lives in Jesus name we pray.
Amen.
Um when no man can buy or sell. Let us
go let us go to our first slide. When no
man can buy or sell. We know that in the
book of revelation we are told of a time
that is
coming. Uh it is described in revelation
13 16 and 17. And it says here and he
causeth all both small and great, rich
and poor, free and bond to receive a
mark in their right hand or in their
foreheads.
and that no man might buy or
sell save he that had the mark or the
name of the beast or the number of his
name. Uh this time period which the book
of Daniel uh 12:1 describes as a time of
trouble such as never was is a very
serious time.
Um it is the time in
which the mark of the beast is
initiated. And the the trouble with the
mark of the beast issue is that those
who refuse the mark will not be able to
buy or
sell. And that's going to be a challenge
for a lot of people. Think about the
ability to or losing the ability to
provide. Provide for your family.
Provide for
yourselves. It is going to be a rough
time. It is a time where no man will be
able to buy or sell. Those who refuse
the mark will not be able to buy or
sell. In Luke 21, uh Luke 21, the Bible
tells us, speaking of this time, uh it
says, "Men's hearts will be failing them
for fear and for looking after those
things which are coming upon the earth,
for the powers of heaven shall be
shaken." The very next verse reads, "And
they shall see the son of man coming in
a cloud with power and great glory." So
the Bible lets us know that during this
time of the mark of the beast in which
no man can buy or sell
um
they men's hearts will be failing them
for
fear. Now God's people will not be
afraid. Those who are trusting in God
will not be afraid. Their hearts will
not be failing them for fear. Even
though there is a decree that says you
are unable to buy or sell unless you
receive the mark, they will not fear. In
fact, Psalm
91 describes the attitude of the
righteous. Note with me, Psalm 91, we're
going to read verses 1-6. The Bible
says, "He that dwelleth in the secret
place of the most high shall abide under
the shadow of the Almighty. I will say
of the Lord, he is my refuge and my
fortress, my God. In him will I trust.
Surely he shall deliver thee from the
snare of the fowler, and from the
noisome pestilence. He shall cover thee
with his
feathers, and under his wings shalt thou
trust. His truth shall be thy shield and
thy buckler. Thou shalt not be afraid
for the terror by night, nor for the
arrow that flieth by day, nor for the
pestilence that walketh in darkness, nor
for the destruction that wasteth at
noonday. God's people will not be
afraid. Put a one in the chat. Put a one
in the chat if you say amen to that.
During this time when no one who
receives the mark
uh who does not receive the mark uh will
be able to buy or sell. God says though
other people's hearts around will be
failing for fear because of the
calamities coming upon the earth. God's
people will not be afraid. God's people
will not be afraid. Now y'all put put
a put a two in the chat. Put a two in
the chat. If you are looking, if you
are
seriously
concerned with what will happen in that
time, like in that time when no man can
buy or sell because of this decree and
you're saying, "I want to be ready and
prepared for when this time comes that I
won't be able to go to the store and buy
have my vegetables. I won't be able to
go to the
store and get clothing. I won't be able
to go to the store and get the food that
I need. What is that going to be like?
And how can I prepare for that time when
no man can buy or
sell? That is a serious question. It is
a serious question. and and as
Adventists and as Christians all around,
we should be concerned about being
prepared for that
time. But might I suggest to you
that being prepared for that time in
which no man can buy or sell is
different than a lot of us
think. Because for many of us, we're
wondering, how am I going to survive
when I cannot go to the store or cannot
use my my card or cannot use cash to get
anything? How am I going to survive in
that time?
But I want to suggest to you that there
is a greater concern that you and I
should
have. Because though there is a decree
that is coming in which no man can buy
or sell except he receive the mark of
the beast, there is another decree that
we should be more concerned about. And
that decree is also about when no man
can buy or
sell. Let me tell you what I'm talking
about. Come with me to Revelation
3:14. And I want you to note what the
Bible says here. Revelation 3 and verse
14. The Bible says, "And unto the angel
of the church of the Leodysians, write
these things, sayith the Amen, the
faithful and true witness, the beginning
of the creation of God. I know thy works
that thou art neither cold nor hot, I
would that thou were cold or hot. So
then, because you are lukewarm, neither
cold nor hot, I will spew thee out of my
mouth, because thou sayest, I am rich,
and increase with goods, and have need
of
nothing,
and knowest not that thou art wretched,
and miserable, and poor, and blind, and
naked. And now I want you to note these
next
words. I counsel thee to buy. Put that
word in the chat for me. Please put that
word in the chat. I'mma finish reading
the text, but I just need you to put
that word in the chat. I counsel thee to
buy of me gold tried in the
fire that thou mayest be rich, and white
reignment that thou mayest be clothed,
and that the shame of thy nakedness do
not appear, and anoint thine eyes with
eyes, that thou mayest see. So I want
you to note here that God in speaking to
the last day church, the Leodysian
church, God says,
"Listen, I am encouraging you to buy of
me and I'm encouraging you to do that
soon, to do that
ASAP." Now, why would God encourage us
to buy and to buy now? to buy
today. Because may I suggest to
you that while the devil issues a decree
in which no man can buy or sell save he
that has the mark, at the same time, God
will be issuing a decree that no man can
buy or sell save he that has the seal.
May I suggest to
you that while the devil is putting a
decree out, will put a decree out in
which if you receive the unless you
receive the mark, you will not be able
to buy or sell. that at the same time
God will be putting out a decree that
says unless you have the seal you will
not be able to buy or
sell. In other words, there is coming a
time
where if you have not bought what God is
asking you to
buy. There is coming a time where the
opportunity to buy will be shut off,
will be closed. Are y'all with me be?
Are y'all with me? Are y'all
understanding what I'm
saying? While we should be concerned
about not being able to buy or sell in
temporal things, there is a greater
concern that should occupy our minds,
which is not being able to buy what God
is asking us to buy of him.
Now, y'all put a five in the chat. If
you are following the foundation that
I've just laid, well, what does God want
us to buy? I want you to note the three
things according to first Peter chapter
3. Remember, he said, "I need you to buy
of me gold." Why gold? The Bible says,
"Blessed be the God and Father of our
Lord Jesus Christ, which according to
his abundant mercy has begotten us again
unto a lively hope by the resurrection
of Jesus Christ from the dead, to an
inheritance incorruptible and undefiled,
and that fadeth not away, reserved in
heaven for
you who are
kept by the power of God through faith
unto salvation, ready to be revealed in
the last time. So the text is saying
that there is going to be a keeping
power of the of the people of God in the
very last time. And what is that keeping
power? It is faith. Faith is that
keeping power. Let's keep reading. So,
so again it says, "Who are kept by the
power of God through faith unto
salvation, ready to be revealed in the
last time, wherein you greatly rejoiced,
though now for a season, if need be, you
are in heaviness through manifold
temptation." And watch this. That the
trial of your faith, being much more
precious than of gold that
perisheth, though it be tried with fire,
might be found unto praise and honor and
glory at the appearing of Jesus Christ,
whom having not seen, you love, in whom,
though now you see him not, yet
believing you rejoice with joy
unspeakable and full of glory, receiving
the end of your faith, even the
salvation of your souls. So everything
we just read says to us that the reason
why God wants us to buy gold is because
gold is symbolic of faith. And faith
will be
required in the last time in that time
of trouble in that time where only those
who receive the mark will be able to buy
or sell. God says, "Those who have faith
in this time will stand against this
time of trouble." will stand in this
time of trouble. Why? Because they
bought while they could
buy. They bought while they could
buy. What about the oil? What about the
oil? Let's go back to the screen.
Zechariah 4:1.
Zechariah is in vision here. The Bible
says, "And the angel who spake with me
came again and woke me like a man
awakened from sleep and said unto me,
what seeest thou?" And I said, I I've
looked, and behold, a candlestick of all
all of gold with a bowl on the top of
it, and his seven lamps thereon, and
seven pipes to the seven lamps which are
on top thereof, and two olive trees by
it, one upon the right side of the bowl,
and the other upon the left side of it.
So he sees this candlestick, this lamp,
and then there are two olive trees on
either side of the lamp. The text goes
on to say, the text goes on to say, "So
I answered and spake to the angel that
talked with me, saying, "What are these,
my Lord?" Then the angel that talked
with me answered and said unto me,
Knowest thou not what these be? And I
said, "No, my Lord." And then he
answered and spake unto me, saying, This
is the word of the Lord unto Zerubbabel,
saying, Not by might, nor by power, but
by my spirit, saith the Lord. Who art
thou, oh great mountain, before
Zerubbabel, thou shalt become a plain,
and they shall bring forth the headstone
thereof, shouting, grace, grace unto it.
Why do we need the oil? Because beloved,
the oil represents the Holy Spirit. And
it is the Holy Spirit then that allows
our fire to keep burning even in that
time of trouble
where
only or those who do not receive the
mark of the beast will not be able to
buy or sell. And this is why Jesus is
inviting us to buy of him now.
by
gold, by the
oil, by the white raignment. That was
the third thing mentioned in Revelation
chapter 3, the white raignment. Notice
with me, Revelation 19:8. Revelation
19:8, the Bible says, "And to her was
granted that that she should be arrayed
in fine linen, clean and white, for the
fine linen is the righteousness of the
saints." Do you see what God is doing
here? He's saying, "I need you to buy of
me righteousness. I need you to buy of
me gold, faith. I need you to buy of me
oil." That's the Holy Spirit. I need you
to buy these things of me. What is the
white linen? It is the righteousness of
the saints which in
actuality notice with with me with me
Genesis 15:6 the Bible says and he
believed speaking of Abraham he believed
in the Lord and he counted it to him for
righteousness. Do you
see God is trying to make sure that our
belief, our faith is strong in him. And
so and so God says, "I need you to buy
of me gold. I need you to buy of me oil.
I need you to buy of me white
raignment." Why white raignment? It is
the righteousness of Christ. And by the
way, all who are found with the white
raignment provide the evidence that they
have not listened to the lies of
Satan. When God spoke to Adam and Eve in
the
garden and they were
naked and knew that they were naked. The
reason why they were naked is because
they had listened to the word of Satan
over the word of God. So the white
raignment is evidence that we are not
listening to Satan. The oil is evidence
that the Holy Spirit is in us and the
gold is evidence that we are walking by
faith. These are the things that God has
invited us to buy of him. Why? Because
beloved, because there is a time coming.
In fact, let me read this. Jeremiah
23:6. Let's go to the screen. In the
days of Judah shall be saved. In the
days in his days, Judah shall be saved.
Israel shall dwell sa safely. And this
is the name whereby he shall be called
the Lord our righteousness. The Lord is
our
righteousness. Where to buy the gold,
that's faith. We're to buy the oil,
that's the Holy Spirit. And where to buy
the white raignment, which is the
covering of Christ in us now. Now, why
are we to buy and why are we to buy now?
Let me show you. There is a time coming
where Jesus will say, "He that is
unjust, let him be unjust still. And he
which is filthy, let him be filthy
still. And he that is righteous, let him
be righteous still. And he that is holy,
let him be holy still." In other words,
beloved, just as Satan issues a decree
that says, "Now nobody can buy or sell
except they receive the mark, so God has
his own decree. Let him who is righteous
be righteous still. Let him who is
filthy be filthy still." And in that
time of that decree, there is no more
ability to do what you could have done
before.
It is now too late. In fact, you all may
remember a parable found in Matthew
chapter 25. Let's go there. Matthew
chapter 25, beginning with verse 6. The
parable of the 10 virgins in which five
were wise and five were foolish. And at
midnight, the Bible says, there was a
cry made, "Behold, the bridegroom
cometh, go you out to meet him." Then
all those virgins arose and trimmed
their lamps. And the foolish said unto
the wise, Give us of your oil, for our
lamps are gone out. But the wise
answered, saying, Not so, lest there be
not enough for us and you. But go ye
rather to them that sell and buy for
yourselves. Buy for yourselves. Beloved,
understand that by the time these five
foolish virgins go to buy for
themselves, the sales are already over.
When they come back, it is already too
late. Whoever they bought from, it
wasn't Jesus. Whatever oil they got, it
wasn't the Holy Spirit. They had passed
the time that heaven was open for
business. Faith
business. So God says, "I need you to
buy now." So, so now that we understand,
oh wow, there's a there's a time where I
will no longer be able to buy the things
that God is saying I need for the time
of trouble, then I better buy now. So,
now our question is, well, okay, how
shall we
buy? What does it mean to
buy? Well, to
buy, what do you need in order to
buy? Let me ask it that way. What does
everyone need in order to buy? And what
can you not buy
without? You cannot buy
without. Come on y'all. You cannot buy.
If you go to the store today and you
say, "I'd like to buy
something." What do you need in order to
buy that thing?
You
need
money. You need money. You need
currency. You cannot
buy without
currency. Listen to what the Bible says
in Matthew chapter 19:1 16. The Bible
says here, "And behold, one came and
said unto him, good master, what good
thing shall I do that I may may inherit
eternal life?" And he said unto him,
"Why callst thou me good? There is none
good but one, that is God. But if thou
wil enter into life, keep the
commandments." And he saith unto him,
which Jesus said, "Thou shalt do no
murder. Thou shalt not commit adultery.
Thou shalt not steal. Thou shalt not
bear false witness. Honor thy father and
thy mother, and thou shalt love thy
neighbor as
thyself." And the young man said unto
him, "All these things have I kept from
my youth. What lack?" Now, do y'all
remember the name of this story? What's
the name of this story? What do they
call this story in the
Bible? It is a story about the what? The
something something
ruler. Y'all put it in the chat. What is
this story about? It's the story of
the
rich
young
ruler. Notice what the Bible says.
Notice what the Bible says in the next
verse. So Jesus said unto
him, "If thou wil be perfect,
go and
sell what you have and give to the poor,
and thou shalt have treasure in heaven,
and come and follow me." But when the
young man heard that saying, he went
away and was sorrowful, for he had great
possessions. How do we get treasure in
heaven? Because that's what the text
said. In order to get treasure in
heaven, what do we first need to do?
What do we first need to do if we want
treasure in heaven? So, what would the
treasure in heaven be? Maybe the white
raignment, maybe the oil, maybe the
gold.
What would we need to
do according to what we just
read? Jesus said, "Go and put that word
in chat." I should I You know what? I
should have called it just called this
sermon
sell. Go and sell. The secret to buying
is selling. Put that in the chat for me,
y'all. Please. The secret to
buying is selling. If I want to buy,
I've got to first sell. H listen,
listen. Now, we're not talking about
sell things for money. Because remember
Isaiah 55:1 says, "Oh, everyone that
thirsteth, come ye to the waters. He
that hath no money, come ye buy and eat.
Yay, come buy wine and milk without
money and without price." So God is not
saying here that you need actual money
in order to
buy. No, this is this is this is
spiritual. This is spiritual. So so so
God is saying I need you all if you want
treasure in heaven. I need you to start
selling some stuff
off. Y'all put a five in the chat if you
begin to see where I'm going. God is
saying, "I need y'all to sell some
stuff. I need you to I need you all to
sell some things. If you want treasure
in heaven, the first thing you must do
is sell. In order to buy, you have to
sell. The Bible says in Luke
18:4, Luke 18:4, when Jesus saw that
they were very s that he was very
sorrowful, he said, "How hardly shall
they that have riches enter into the
kingdom of
God?" Oh, we got to get rid of our
riches. Yes. So, what are our riches?
That's the question. What are our
riches? What is it that we have to sell?
What is it that we are in possession of
that God is saying, "If you want to
follow me, sell these things." Listen to
what the Bible says in Matthew chapter 6
19. Matthew chapter 6:1 19. The Bible
says, "Lay not up for yourselves
treasures upon the earth, where moth and
rust does corrupt, and wherein thieves
break through and steal, but lay up for
yourselves treasures in heaven. Where
neither moth nor moth nor rust does
corrupt, and where thieves do not break
through nor steal." And now watch this
next verse. For where your treasure is,
there will your heart be also.
From this verse, we can assume
something. We can begin to understand
something that if we want to know what
our treasure is, all we have to do is
look at where our heart is.
Because now we understand that for the
purpose of this sermon, we're not
talking about sell your sneakers, sell
your computer, sell your home, sell
physical things. We're talking about
selling something that is not
physical. And how do we find out what
that is? Well, the text says, "Where
your treasure is, there will your heart
be
also." Now, I need y'all to understand
that the Bible says, "The heart is
deceitful and wicked." So, huh, I wonder
then if what God is trying to tell me is
he's trying to tell me to sell the
things that my heart treasures. Why?
Because my heart is deceitful and
wicked.
Ah. Oh, wait a minute. Oh, you know
what? Now this begins to make sense.
Look at this. Luke
6:45. The Bible says here, "A good man
out of the good treasure of his heart
bringeth forth that which is good, and
an evil man out of the evil treasure of
his heart bringeth forth that which is
evil. For of the abundance of the heart
the mouth speaketh." I get it now,
beloved. Could it be that what God is
trying to get us to sell is the tr the
evil treasures that are located in the
heart? Did y'all catch that just
now? God wants us to sell the evil
treasure that is within our hearts. the
things that are holding us back from
fully following after God, our
possessions. Come on. Come on. Note with
me Matthew 7 21, which makes it even
clearer. Matthew 7 21 the Bible says,
"For within the heart of man proceed
what are those evil treasures? evil
thoughts,
adulteries,
fornications,
murders, thefts, covetousness,
wickedness, deceit, lasciviousness, an
evil eye. Y'all remember last week's
sermon? Y'all remember last week's
sermon, an evil eye? Remember how Saul
had that evil eye toward David? And
everything that David
did, Saul would go make a video about
it.
Everything that David did, Saul had a
way to twist it to make it evil. Evil
eye. God says these are the things that
come from an evil heart.
Blasphemy, pride, foolishness, all these
things come from within and defile the
man. Listen to me,
y'all. Listen to what God is
saying. You guys, I need you to sell
your
possessions. I need you to sell your
possessions because without selling your
possessions, you can't buy what I'm
trying to give
you. You can't
buy what I am selling you.
Do you have
anger to somebody
else? Yeah, that's my possession though.
You You're not trying to take that from
me. And I'm not trying to take it from
you. I'm asking you to sell it. I will
never take anything from you by force.
I will never take anything away from
you against your will. So, I need you to
sell
it. Wait a minute. What? This is a
longunning feud. What do you mean sell
it? I've invested in
this. God says, "I need you to sell
it. I need you to sell your anger. I
need you to sell your bitterness. I need
you to sell your resentment. I need you
to sell I need you to sell your your
hatred. I need you to sell your pride. I
need you to sell your covetousness. I
need you to sell these things because in
selling these things, this is your
demonstration that you are really intent
on buying what I have for you. Yes,
Takora, sell your
superpower. Remember what happened in
Genesis 6:5. The Bible says, "And God
saw that the wickedness of man was great
in the earth, and that every imagination
of the thoughts of his heart was only
evil continually." Man was
enriched with
sin. He was rich in anger. He was rich.
And that's how it's going to be at the
end of time. So, what I want you to
understand, beloved, is
this. Those who are able to stand in the
time of the mark of the beast and not be
worried about buying and selling in that
time is because they are already rich.
And the way they got rich was by
selling. Y'all put a seven in the chat
if you follow what I'm saying. The way
they got rich in heavenly things was
that they sold everything
earthly. They sold everything of the
flesh. Yes. Whoso loses his life for my
sake. I saw you put the text in the
chat. Whoso loses his life for my sake
will find it. Now listen to me y'all.
This is why the Bible says, watch this.
Now come back with me to the screen.
In 1 Timothy chapter 6:10, the Bible
says, "For the love of money is the root
of all evil." And I hope, beloved,
you're beginning to understand here that
it's not necessarily God saying the love
of the dollar bill. What he's saying is
the love of riches. And now riches
extends beyond the dollar bill. It
extends beyond the love of
riches. Wow.
Okay. Okay. Now I see what you're
saying. It is the love of earthly
riches, not just the dollar
bill, but the love of earthly riches,
the things that I think will enrich my
life, the things of the flesh. It is the
love of riches that is the root of all
evil.
Are y'all catching
this? We don't want to give up the
things that in a worldly sense enrich
our
lives. Yeah, I like that. Somebody put a
dollar sign s i n but the s is in the
dollar sign. I like that. I like that.
The love of riches you all is the root
of all evil. Now let me show let me
prove that to you. The love of self
where the treasure where the heart is
there where will your treasure be also.
So if the heart is the is the treasure,
if the wickedness of man is in the heart
and that's the
treasure, then it is love of
self because I am more valuable to me
than anything else on the planet. And
whatever self wants, we're going to make
that
happen. Let me show you. Come with me to
Ezekiel chapter 28. Ezekiel chapter 28.
And let's really see if the love of
riches was really the root of all
evil. Thou has been in the garden in the
Eden, the garden of God. Speaking of
Lucifer. And then it says something
really, really amazing, y'all. It says,
"Every
precious stone was thy
covering." Do y'all see that?
Lucifer was
covered with precious. That word
precious literally means
costly. Lucifer was expensively
made. Every precious stone was thy
covering. The sardis, the topaz, the
diamond, the barrel, the onyx, the
jasper, the sapphire, the emerald, the
carbuncle, and
gold. The workmanship of thy tabts and
of thy pipes was prepared in thee in the
day that was that thou was created. And
then notice the next text. Thou was
perfect in thy ways from the day that
was that thou was created until iniquity
was found in
thee. And now watch this. By the
multitude of thy
merchandise. What was the
merchandise? What was the
merchandise? He was the merchandise,
y'all. He was the merchandise. He began
to look at
himself. Man, you know
what? I I I like this treasure. He began
to look at himself and then began to
merchandise
himself. He was selling himself to
everybody, selling himself to the
angels. Self became the
treasure.
His love of this treasure became the
root of all
evil. He's selling himself. He was his
treasure. He began to love himself more
than he loved God.
And so now we begin to learn that when
we become our own
treasure, when we become our own
treasure, when we become the richest
thing to us in our lives, the love of
self, where your heart is, there will
your treasure be also. Now we're trying
to guard the treasure.
And what God is saying to you is, I need
you to sell your
treasure. Let me rephrase that. I need
heart. I need
you to sell it. Let Let me break this
down even further, you
guys. So, in order to buy faith, we have
to sell doubt.
Did
y'all five in the chat if you caught
that just
now? If I want to buy faith, I have to
sell doubt. So remember Jesus on the
boat uh uh with the disciples.
Immediately Jesus stretched forth his
hand and caught him and and said unto
him, "Oh, thou of little faith,
wherefore did thou doubt? If I want to
buy faith gold, I've got to sell
doubt. Lord, I'm giving up my doubt. I'm
selling
it. I'm selling it. Why? Because the
more doubt I sell is the more faith I
buy. Yes. Yes.
Yes. The more doubt I sell, and man, I
am rich in doubt. I got a lot of doubt.
You listen, I got doubt for
days. I am rich in it. But if I start to
sell off my
doubt, the end result is that I'm buying
belief. I cannot buy belief without
first selling
doubt. Are y'all with me? So, so God
says, "Come on, y you guys, there's
coming a time where you're not going to
be able to buy or sell. So, I've got to
sell. I've got to give it away. I've got
to say, I'm giving this up. I'm selling
it. I'm selling doubt. If I want oil,
watch this. If I want to buy
oil, then I've got to sell the
flesh. If I want to buy the spirit, I've
got to sell away the flesh. Let me break
it down. Let's go to the screen.
Galatians chapter 5:1 16.
I was did not intend to rhyme there. But
listen to what the Bible
says. Then I this I say
then walk in the spirit and you shall
not fulfill the lust of the
flesh. For the flesh lusteth against the
spirit and the spirit against the flesh.
And these are contrary one to the other.
so that you cannot do the things that
you would. So beloved, if I want the
spirit, I've got to sell the things of
the flesh. And what are the things of
the flesh? Yes, Eric, let's use another
word for release. I've got to release
these things. I've got to sell
them. Let me talk about this works of
the flesh. What are the works of the
flesh? Now the works of the flesh are
manifest which are these adultery,
fornication, unclean uh lasciviousness,
idolatry, witchcraft, hatred, variance,
emulations, wrath, stripes, seditions.
That's what God is. You sell these
things. The more you sell these things
is the more you're buying of the spirit.
God is trying to get us to buy and sell
while heaven is open for business. Sell
your
grudges.
Sell
your
grudges.
Sell your
unforgiveness. Sell your
wrath. Sell
Sell, sell,
sell. The Bible says in Matthew 6:24,
"No man can serve two masters, for
either he will hate the one and love the
other, or else he will hold to the one
and despise the other." You cannot serve
God and riches. You cannot serve God and
mammon. You've got to let it go. Jesus
said again in Matthew 13:21, Jesus said,
"If you will be perfect, go and sell
what you have and give to the poor." and
thou shalt have treasure in heaven. The
secret to having treasure in heaven is
to sell it
all. Sell
it. Sell
it. Walk away from
it. So then, watch
this. Just as in the time of the mark,
let me put it back up on the screen.
Revelation 13:16, he causth all, both
small and great, rich and poor, free and
bond, to receive a mark in their right
hand or in their foreheads. And that no
man might buy or sell, watch this now,
save he that had the mark of the name or
the name of the beast or the number of
his name. It's not that no one can buy
or sell anymore. It's that no one can
buy or sell except those that have the
mark. Well, beloved, in the same way,
that stands for God's decree.
No one will be able to do business with
God anymore except they have the name of
God and his
seal. So it's not God saying, "Hey, you
can no longer do transactions with me."
It's God saying only those who are
sealed are now going to be able to buy
of me. And I notice I didn't say sell. I
said only those who are sealed will
still be able to buy of
me. Why will they still be able to buy
of him? In other words, why will he
continue to provide faith for them? Why
will he continue to provide oil for them
in this time? Why will he continue to
provide the white garment for them? Why
will he even pour out extra upon them?
talk to Cory, you beat me to the punch
because I was going to say it. We need
to have a yard
sale. We need to have a yard sale. You
know when you you know when you have a
yard sale, what are you doing? You're
getting rid of the unnecessary stuff out
of your
house, out of the
storehouse, garage
sale. You're getting rid of the stuff
you don't need anymore. Now listen to me
y'all because I know what most of y'all
think. Many of y'all think, "Oh, this
garage sale, I'm putting this person out
there and this person out there and cuz
I don't want to see them. I don't want
to talk to them. I'm tired of them. I
don't need them in my life." That's not
the garage sale I'm talking about. The
garage sale I'm talking about is selling
things, not selling
people. You're trying to get rid of the
junk in your own heart.
So come back. Watch this. Now the the
reason that God's people will not have
anything left to sell in that time is
because they sold
everything. They sold it
all. They have nothing left to sell.
Which means if they have nothing left to
sell, they have all the money in the
world to buy and buy and
buy. And now they're buying extra grace
and extra gold and extra oil and extra
raymond. Why? Because in the time of
trouble, we are going to need a grace
that we do not now possess. We're going
to need a level of the spirit that we do
not now possess. Why? because that time
is going to be a greater time of trouble
than any other time previously. Listen
to me. Listen to me here. What the Bible
says in Matthew 13:45 and 46. Again, the
kingdom of heaven is like unto a
merchant man seeking goodly pearls, who
when he had found one pearl of great
price, went and sold.
How
much How much did he sell? He sold
out. He sold
out. God is calling you to be a
sellout. God is calling you to sell
everything out. Sell everything out. The
devil doesn't want to say, "Man, don't
be a sellout. Don't sell my stuff."
God is calling us to
sell
everything. Sell it
all. So then those who sell it all,
those who in the yard sale, the spring
cleaning, or if we want to use biblical
terms, the fall
cleaning, day of
atonement, day of atonement is the
garage sale. You
guys, the day of atonement, the day of
atonement is the garage sale that
prepares us to get what we need to stand
in the time of trouble. Yes, Jerry.
Going out of business
sale, everything must
go. Back in the day in New York, there
was that Crazy Eddie message. Y'all
remember that Crazy Eddie? And Crazy
Eddie had to get rid of everything in
the store. Everything had to
go. Beloved, God is calling us to sell
everything to go out of
business. We're not doing business.
We're not holding the devil's furniture
stuff anymore. We're not holding his his
riches. We're selling it all. What does
that mean? It means selling out
animosity. It means selling
unforgiveness. It means selling your
grudges. God is. And beloved, I believe
that that's why God is Satan is really
trying to
just if he can
get us as members of the
church to attempt to destroy, to be
angry with, to hold
grudges, and then issues that decree
that no man can buy or sell.
Do y'all understand
this?
Everyone, anyone who has any
stuff left to sell and the mark of the
beast is issued, you are going to don't
ask me how. Just
saying. You will end up receiving the
mark. Why? because you still had stuff
that you had to sell. And that's what
the devil is banking
on. Because those who still have stuff
to sell will end up being so
terrified of this physical challenge of,
"Oh, I can't buy food. I can't buy
whatever because I'm not trusting in
God. I don't know what it means to trust
in God. I don't know what it means to
have that kind of faith. I don't know
what it means to have that kind of that
that kind of spirit because I'm used to
walking in the flesh. I'm used to
getting angry. I'm used to allowing my
anger to get the best of me. I'm used to
it. Understand what I'm saying? When the
righteous have sold
all, now they have limitless funds to
buy from God something that they cannot
get except in that time. Let me let me
tell you what I'm talking about. And
we're almost done. We're almost done.
Hebrews chapter 4:16, the Bible says,
"Let us therefore come boldly unto the
throne of grace that we may obtain, get
a hold of, obtain mercy, and to find
grace to help in the time of need." I'm
going to end with a with a statement
here with a quote from Ellen White, and
you'll see what I'm talking you will see
what I
mean about what I just said about
needing extra grace in that time. grace
that we do not now have. Y'all ready?
Here we go. Here we go. Last last set of
slides here. Last quote is from the
Desire of Ages, page
354. The disciples were not endowed with
the courage and fortitude of the martyrs
until such grace was needed.
I can stop right
there. I'm not even going to read the
rest of the quote. I can stop right
there. When we wonder about the martyrs,
like how did they how were they able to
go through that
trial? Elsewhere, she says they didn't
always have that faith.
It was at the moment that they needed
that kind of faith that they were
supplied with that kind of
faith. None of us right now
possess the
faith that will be necessary to make it
in the time of
trouble. Right now, God gives us grace
sufficient for the crisis. He gives us
grace sufficient for what is a for for
what we're going through at the moment.
But the world is coming to a place where
Jesus said it'll be a time of trouble
such as never was. And beloved, in that
time, we are going to need much more
grace than we need for, let's say,
somebody cut me off while I was driving
and it made me really remember last week
how we talked about this this false
spirit of persecution in America today.
I was
forced. Uh they're taking away
Christmas. You can't say Christmas. What
shall we do? Woe is me. Remember we
talked about
that last week or the week before? I
think it was last week.
And the Bible says, "If the footmen have
wearied you, how will you do in the time
of the
horsemen?" Of the
horses. In the time of trouble, beloved,
only
those who are still able to
buy are going to get the grace that is
needed for the time of trouble. Yeah.
Let not your heart be troubled. Don't
think to yourself, I don't know if I
have what it takes to make it through
the time of trouble. No, right now, you
don't have what it takes because we're
not in the time of trouble. But when
that time of trouble hits, God is going
to pour out more grace. But he's only
pouring out more grace for those five
wise virgins. The ones, listen to me,
the
ones who sold
everything, so that in that time they
could buy and buy and buy and buy and
buy.
So in conclusion, you all
Sell
it. Sell it
all. Sell it before the time comes where
no man can buy or
sell except he
that. And you fill in the blank. You
fill in the blank. He that has the
mark or he that has a seal. Two groups
of people, two
decrees. Which group of people are you
going to be
in? That's right, Faith. You need to
sell everything before the close of
probation. Sell it all. Have a yard
sale. Have a yard sale. If you need to
do a weekly yard sale, do a weekly yard
sale.
sell it. What does it profit a man if he
gains the whole
world and yet
loses his own
soul? Y'all put that one in the chat if
you are looking forward to having
daily weekly yard art sales until you
sell everything. Put that one in the
chat. Pastor, I got so much stuff in my
house. You You wouldn't believe it.
You're right. I need to do some spring
cleaning, some fall
cleaning. I need to I got a bunch of
stuff I need to sell.
I see the ones coming in the chat. I see
the ones coming in the chat. That is
your standing up. That is you standing
up before the Lord today and saying,
"Yes,
Lord. Yard sale. Yard
sale. It's time to
sell." Heavenly Father, thank you for
speaking to us.
Thank you Lord for showing us that there
is a time
coming where no one will be able to buy
or sell from
you unless they have the seal of God in
their foreheads.
Please
Lord, teach us to sell everything that
we have now that we might purchase the
treasure of
heaven that we may purchase the Isalve,
the gold, the white raignment.
Teach us, Lord, to sell our treasure
before it is too
late. So that we might buy the treasures
of heaven in a time where there will be
spiritual poverty across the whole
world. May we be rich in that
time. Grant us the grace we will need to
stand in that time. And we thank you
Lord for your desire to see every one of
us
saved. Lord, I want to pray a special
prayer for anyone who especially inside
the living man of church or outside the
living man of
church who have riches that they need to
sell.
[Music]
animosity,
anger,
bitterness,
unforgiveness to one
another. Please, dear
Jesus, help help
them to sell it
all and not try to go back and buy
it. I don't know. I shouldn't have got
rid of that. I want to go back and buy
it. Help them to sell it and not return.
Not ask for a
refund. Please Lord, let us not ask for
a
refund. Let us sell it and leave
it. And we thank you,
Lord. We thank
you for what you are selling
us. Or we thank you that you're not
selling it for money.
You're selling it for
us. You want
us. So Lord, please redeem your
people and we thank you and love you. In
Jesus name we pray. Amen. And
amen. All sales final. Amen. So you
guys, you can look in the chat, you will
see the slide. If you would like a copy
of these sermon slides, you'll see it
right there in the chat. Hit on that
link. I want to again encourage you guys
if you have not um
um subscribed to Living Mana YouTube
channel. Uh make sure you do that as
well. Um if there's any of you that are
interested in beginning to study the
Bible, perhaps to be baptized
um or to join the church by profession
of faith. Uh I'm I'm hoping that we can
put that slide up where people can get
in touch with our Bible worker. Um, and
it should be uh Bible worker at um uh at
Living Mana. Let's see if we can get
that up there. At least get it in the
slide. And then lastly, we're going to
put the link in the chat for our
afterglow. Um, please feel free to join
us. We're going to talk about what we
learned in Sabbath school. We're going
to talk about what you got from the
sermon. So, this is where we fellowship
and you know, we invite you all to to
fellowship with us. This is not just for
the Living Mana Church members, but for
everyone. So um it's a beautiful time
that we come together and we just share
how the Lord has inspired us um through
the message. And again uh thank you for
joining us. May God bless you. May God
keep you and we will see you again next
week. Share this message. Share this
sermon. May God bless you. Till we meet
again. Amen.